The Best
I call you when
I need you my heart's on fire
You come to me come to me wild and wired
Ooh you come to me
Give me everything
I need
Give me a lifetime of promises and a world of dreams
Speak a language of love like you know what it means
Mmm and it can't be wrong
Take my heart and make it strong
You're simply the best
Better than all the rest
Better than anyone
Anyone I've ever met
I'm stuck on your heart
I hang on every word you say
Tear us apart
Baby I would rather be dead
In your heart
I see the start of every night and every day
In your eyes
I get lost
I get washed away
Just as long as
I'm here in your arms
I could be in no better place
You're simply the best
Better than all the rest
Better than anyone
Anyone I've ever met ooh
I'm stuck on your heart
I hang on every word you say
Tear us apart no, no, no baby
I would rather be dead
Each time you leave me
I start losing control
You're walking away with my heart and my soul
I can feel you even when
I'm alone oh baby don't let go
Ooh you're the best, ooh better than all the rest
Better than anyone
Anyone I've ever met ooh
I'm stuck on your heart
I hang on every word you say
Tear us apart, no, no baby
I would rather be dead oh you're the best